



#### **About Me**

I believe a good designer and developer should be able to use technology to create new solutions, interfaces and experiences that solve human needs to make life easier and worth living. Address : Shomolu, Yaba, Lagos state, Nigeria.

Nationality : Nigerian

Interest : UI/UX, Data Science, Business

Intelligence, Science & Technology

# **Education And Experience**



#### **Education**

# Interaction Design Specialization

University of California San Diego

Aug 2020 - Sept 2020

# Business Analysis Career Start

IT Masters,

**Charles Sturt University** 

June 2020 - August 2020

# BSC Information Communication & Technology

Ghana Institute of Management and Public Administration, Accra, Ghana

2015 - 2019

I took courses on Fundamentals of proggramming, Object Oriented Programming using C#, Calculus, Discrete Mathematics, Probability and Statistics, Project Management, Data warehousing and Data mining,

Relational Database, System Administration, Human Computer Interaction.



#### **Experience**

### o 2019 - Present

### **UI/UX Designer And Developer**

Optisoft Company Limited

Lagos Island, Lagos, Nigeria

• Design of cross platform products, with close involvement from product owners and development team implementing my designs

# Oct 2019 - Present

# Software Engineer - Remote

KnackApp

San Francisco, California, United States

• I was responsible for bringing figma designs to life

# June 2018 - August 2018

# **Research and Development Intern**

Link Exchange

• I was responsible for designing web interfaces and carrying out research

on new technologies that can be use for a loan project.

# Skills

# Technology skill

I'm proficient with frontend development technologies (HTML, CSS, JS, React JS), Data Analysis tools (IBM SPSS, Excel, Python) and also proficient with major UI/UX design tools (Figma, Invision, Adobe XD), design process (visual design, interaction design, wireframing) and research process User-ability testing, Interviews, Surveys, Personas.

# Interpersonal skill

- Open minded to learning new technologies fast
- Ability to think critically, solve problems creatively and effectively
- Strong collaborative working style, to interface successfully with colleagues and partners from around the business with a range of roles, skills and seniorities
- Good interpersonal and communication skills